KIRAN REGMI

Linux | DevOps | Cloud

PERSONAL INFO:

URL: www.kiranregmi.com

GitHub: www.github.com/kiran-regmi **LinkedIn:** www.linkedin.com/in/kregmi

Email: kiranimani@gmail.com
Telephone: 402-972-1861

TECHNICAL SKILLS:

Operating System:

Linux (RedHat 8), Mac OS, Windows

DevOps Tools:

Git, Jenkins, Maven, Ansible, Docker, Kubernetes

AWS Cloud:

EC2, S3, IAM, Security groups, etc.

Programming Languages:

Python, Java, SQL

Bass Scripting, YAML, JSON

IDEs:

PyCharm, Anaconda (jupyter)

Framework:

Flask, Django

CERTIFICATES OF COMPLETION:

Full Stack Java & MySQL

Interface Web School

Fundamentals of Data Science

Omaha Data Science Academy

IT Leader & Management

AIM Institute

Intermediate Tableau

Omaha Data Science Academy

Agile 101

Metropolitan Community College

Mini-MBA

University of Nebraska

AWS Certified Solutions Architect

In progress

EDUCATION:

BS, Business Management (pending) Bellevue University, Bellevue, NE

INTRODUCTION:

Spent 2+ years developing the skills to increase velocity, reliability and quality for SDLC. Experience with Python, AWS, Docker, Kubernetes & Jenkins, getting ready to help organizations instill DevOps for the modern age to save time and money through automation.

PERSONAL / SCHOOL EXPERIENCE:

- Installed and configured Jenkins, Maven, Docker, Kubernetes and Ansible
- Configured and provisioned different ports for Jenkins and Tomcat servers
- Created Snapshot, Images (AMI), implemented Load Balancing and Auto Scaling
- Maintained Git workflow for version control (SCM)
- Built CI/CD Pipeline for code deployment using Jenkins
- Created Docker image, stored in Docker hub and deployed to Kubernetes
- Built and deployed Docker containers for implementing microservices
- Wrote scripts in YAML to automate systems updates
- Created IAM, Security groups features on AWS
- Build and deployed portfolio app using python and Flask web framework
- Created a full stack java project tracker application

WORK EXPERIENCE:

One Stops Creates LLC - Project Manager (Contract) - 04/2019 - 07/2019

 Gathered, analyzed client requirements, and recommended services/products.

Contemporary Analysis LLC - Data Scientist (Contract) - 10/2017 - 06/2018

 Created a tableau dashboard on Omaha healthy food supply for one of the leading local non-profit organization, <u>Live Well Omaha</u>

Omaha World Herald Inc. - District Supervisor - 11/2015 - 04/2016

 Oversaw distribution of OWH products throughout the southwest region of the metropolitan Omaha area

Baha Boho LLC - Operation Manager - 10/2011 - 06/2015

 Oversaw four retail stores and their managers. Increased sales by 40%, simultaneously reducing staff cost by 20%

Infogroup Inc. - Supervisor/Project Manager - 06/2006 - 07/2011

 Managed multiple departments, up to 55 associates in the U.S. and 12 associates in India simultaneously